# **MUHAMMAD AQLI NAJIB**

081219041445 | asofu973@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/aqlinajib

Bandung, Indonesia

An undergraduate in industrial engineering who always wants to expand their knowledge about technology. I have some intern experience in Telkom Indonesia and Encrypt Research Group I have a particular interest in graphic design and IT software engineering.

# Work Experiences

### Boarding Labs - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2018 - May 2018

#### Web Developer

Boarding Labs is the fast-growing information technology company based in Bandung, Indonesia. Our company vision is to be the world's contributing company in improving global welfare by providing the best technology solutions for all elements of society.

- Responsible for handling the Backend of e-commerce website such as building database for the website, identify website needs, identify defenciencis on the website, and debugging code
- · Responsible of handling the Frontend of e-commerce website such as designing the layout for the website
- · Make reports on the performance of e-commerce websites

# Enterprise System Engineering Laboratory - Bandung,

Feb 2022 - Present

Indonesia

#### Laboratory Assistant

Enterprise System Engineering Laboratory is one of many laboratories in Major of Industrial Engineering of Telkom University that focused on enterprise resource planning, information system, and decision analysis that integrates engineering and computer knowledge.

- · Assist the head of the laboratory and the supervisor in the process of implementing of the practicum
- · Participate in the development of practical materials
- · Maintain the laboratory equipment and cleanliness

#### PT Telekomunikasi Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

#### Web Developer

PT Telkom Indonesia (Persero) Tbk (Telkom) adalah Badan Usaha Milik Negara (BUMN) yang bergerak di bidang jasa layanan teknologi informasi dan komunikasi (TIK) dan jaringan telekomunikasi di Indonesia.

- Responsible for maintenance microsite innovation day ddb telkom
- · Designing UI microsite innovation day ddb telkom
- Developing new feature in microsite such a connecting post instagram into microsite, make a post grid related to latest post article into other post, and generate long captions post more concise

#### PT Telekomunikasi Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

#### Designer

PT Telkom Indonesia (Persero) Tbk (Telkom) adalah Badan Usaha Milik Negara (BUMN) yang bergerak di bidang jasa layanan teknologi informasi dan komunikasi (TIK) dan jaringan telekomunikasi di Indonesia.

- · Responsible for designing instagram feeds and story
- · Responsible for designing flyer on the landing page

### Dana Pensiun Telkom - Bandung, Indonesia

Jul 2023 - Oct 2023

### Admin Data Management

Dapen Telkom adalah Badan Hukum berupa Dana Pensiun Pemberi Kerja (DPPK) yang menyelenggarakan Program Pensiun Manfaat Pasti bagi Karyawan TELKOM

- Responsible for the design process to voice the mobile pension fund application in the form of posters and flyers
- Responsible for transferring pension participant data into the new database
- · Making decision letter for pension participant
- Make a failure report when a pension participant registers a pension fund application

### **Education Level**

Universitas Telkom - Bandung, Indonesia

Sep 2020 - Jan 2024 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Industrial Engineering, 3.28/4.00

• Actively Participate ini the work program of the industrial engineering association

### **Organisational Experience**

Enterprise System Engineering Laboratory - Bandung, Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Present

- Responsible for computer maintenance such as setting up an installing software and hardware system, diagnosing and troubleshooting computer issues
- · Responsible for maintenance of ensyse website

#### **Ensyse Competition and Research Youth Partner - Bandung**

Web developer

- · Participate in designing UI/UX on Figma for the website
- · Responsible for Frontend of e-commerce website such as designing the layout for the website
- Responsible for the Frontend Landing Page Website such as designing the layout for the website

# Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Hard Skills: PHP, Python, Laravel Framework, CSS, Bootstrap, Adobe Premiere pro, SQL, PostgreSQL, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effect, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, Google Docs, Google Sheets, Google Forms, Google Slides
- Projects (2018): Building e-commerce Website
- Projects (2022): Building Administration Website "Si adem"
- Projects (2021): Building Landing Page "Encrypt" and Administration website "Encrypt"
- · Soft Skills: Team work, Creativity, Communication, Problem solving, Critical thinking, Decision making
- Projects (2023): Backend Increase Administration Website

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022